employeeboss.com 2012-11-26

# Privacy Policy | HiringBoss

##  PLEASE READ THROUGH THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE CREATING YOUR HIRINGBOSS ACCOUNT

HiringBoss offers an uncompromising level of data security and protection. HiringBoss has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy and to explain how we treat the information we collect when you or your computer interact with us. Please take a moment to read through the following information. If you have any questions at all regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

Please note that HiringBoss seeks to follow privacy practices adhering to the Safe Harbor standards.

##  Intellectual Property Rights

  * Hiring Boss does not claim any ownership over any of the content, including any text, data, information or photographs, or other material, that you upload, transmit or store in your Hiring Boss account. We will not use any of your content for any purpose except to provide you with the Service. You own your data exclusively.
  * HiringBoss does not maintain any public or proprietary candidate databases or sell account data to any third-parties.
  * Each client’s account and candidate database is treated as confidential and privileged.
  * All HiringBoss staff who have access to customer candidate data are required to sign a Confidentiality Statement specifying that they will follow our thorough confidentiality guidelines for client data.

##  Personal information

  * A Hiring Boss account is required to access the applicant tracking system and its various features. During the registration process Hiring Boss may ask you to provide certain pieces of personal information. To protect your account from unauthorized access Hiring Boss provides you with a login and password. Please store this Login data in a safe and secure place.
  * Upon registering with HiringBoss, certain pieces of information, such as name, company name or e-mail address may be used to enable us to provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be used to provide online technical support and aid with any troubleshooting.
  * When signing up for a paid HiringBoss account, we may request financial data. Any financial data we collect is used only to bill you for the services you have elected to purchase. If you opt to pay by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card.
  * During your usage of Hiring Boss our servers automatically records certain information about your use of the system. Similar to other web services and Saas products, HiringBoss records information such as account activity and log information, for example, your number of log-ins, browser type, IP-address, date and time of access, cookie ID.
  * We will never disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission, with the exception of the following possible circumstances: 
    * To fulfill your requests for services
    * To protect ourselves from liability
    * To respond to legal process or comply with law
    * In the instance of a with a merger or acquisition of the company.
    * To comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

##  Accessing HiringBoss Account Information.

  * HiringBoss will provide you with the means to ensure that the personally identifiable information relating to your HiringBoss account is correct and current. When you register for an account you will be able to update your personal information from within your account.

##  Information sharing and onward transfer

  * Hiring Boss maintains and processes your account and its contents to provide the Hiring Boss service to you and to constantly improve our services.
  * Hiring Boss may periodically send you information related to your Hiring Boss account or other services.
  * When you send emails to applicants (such as invitations to interviews or offer letters) via the Hiring Boss integrated e-mail system, information such as your Company´s name, your name and email address may automatically be included as part of that email.
  * If you choose to use our ‘Tell A Friend’ referral service, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. HiringBoss will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We use the information you provided for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email invitation.
  * Upon cancellation of your Hiring Boss account, we would be happy to provide a data export. Additional fees may apply.

##  Changes

HiringBoss may periodically update this policy. We will inform you of significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the account’s primary email address or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

When you access HiringBoss, you acknowledge and fully understand the HiringBoss Privacy Statement and consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy agreement, please contact us.

This document was last updated on the 1st August, 2011.
